
const cards = [{
                "question": "A",
                "answer": "a"
            },
            {
                "question": "B",
                "answer": "b"
            },
            {
                "question": "C",
                "answer": "c"
            },
            {
                "question": "D",
                "answer": "d"
            },
            {
                "question": "E",
                "answer": "e"
            },
            {
                "question": "F",
                "answer": "f"
            },
            {
                "question": "G",
                "answer": "g"
            },
            {
                "question": "H",
                "answer": "h"
            },
            {
                "question": "I",
                "answer": "i"
            },
            {
                "question": "J",
                "answer": "j"
            },
            {
                "question": "K",
                "answer": "k"
            },
            {
                "question": "L",
                "answer": "l"
            },
            {
                "question": "M",
                "answer": "m"
            },
            {
                "question": "N",
                "answer": "n"
            },
            {
                "question": "O",
                "answer": "o"
            },
            {
                "question": "P",
                "answer": "p"
            },
            {
                "question": "Q",
                "answer": "q"
            },
            {
                "question": "R",
                "answer": "r"
            }
        ];
module.exports = cards; 
